Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art public programs records, circa 1995-2011 COR0003.5.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Program files, financial records, and calendar productions, 1994-2011; Series 1
  - January 22, 2008 FY2008 Andrea Stillman Ansel Adams, 2008 January 22; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - January 24, 2008 FY2008 The Art of Buying Art With Paige West, 2008 January 24; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - January 24, 2008 FY2008 Perspective Talk: Paul Roth, 2008 January 24; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - January 30, 2008 FY2008 Jane Austen Goes to the Movies, 2008 January 30; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - February 10, 2008 FY2008 CMF's Verge Ensemble, 2008 February 10; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - February 4, 2008 FY2008 Richardson Greenhal on Picasso, 2008 February 4; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - February 13, 2008 FY2008 Deborah Landis: Dressed, 2008 February 13; Series 1 (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - March 5, 2007 FY2007 Modernism Book Club: A Farewell To Arms, 2007 March 5; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - March 7, 2007 FY2007 Panorama of American Architecture, 2007 March 7; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - March 9, 2007 FY2007 Mes: Garth Newel Quartet, 2007 March 9; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - March 19, 2007 FY2007 Robin Givhan, 2007 March 19; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - March 22, 2007 FY2007 Living with Modern Furniture, 2007 March 22; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - March 23, 2007 FY2007 Bus Tour to New York, 2007 March 23; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - March 26, 2007 FY2007 Lindsay PollockL The Girl with the Gallery, 2007 March 26; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - March 29, 2007 FY2007 Paul Greenhalgh on Utopia, 2007 March 29; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - 2007 April 13 27, 2007 FY2007 Mes: Peabody Trio, Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - April 15, 2007 FY2007 Ziva's Spanish Dance Ensemble, 2007 April 15; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - April 16, 2007 FY2007 Ken Burns on Frank Lloyd Wright, 2007 April 16; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - April 18, 2007 FY2007 Modernism Book Club: Light in August, 2007 April 18; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - April 19, 2007 FY2007 Coleprevost Architecture Tour, 2007 April 19; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - April 22, 2007 FY2007 Contemporary Music Forum, 2007 April 22; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - April 23 2007 FY2007 Paul Goldenberger on Philip Johnson, 2007 April 23; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - April 24, 2007 FY2007 Cynthia Rowley: Slim, 2007 April 24; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - April 26, 2007 FY2007 Rita Koning, 2007 April 26; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - April 30, 2007 FY2007 Tim Samuelson on Louis Sullivan, 2007 April 30; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - April 30, 2007 FY2007 John Szarkowski on Louis Sullivan, 2007 April 30; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - May 1, 2007 FY2007 Nora Pouillon, 2007 May 1; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - May 3, 2007 FY2007 Karim Rashid, 2007 May 3; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - May 7, 2007 FY2007 Dana Buchman, 2007 May 7; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - May 10, 2007 Do Not Go Gently, 2007 May 10; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - May 11, 2007 FY2007 Mes: Klavier Trio Amsterdam, 2007 May 11; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - May 14, 2007 FY2007 Modernism Book Club: Invisible Man, 2007 May 14; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - CANCELED May 21, 2007 FY2007 ESTA, 2007 May 21; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - May 24, 2007 FY2007 Eric Denker Judith Martin on Venice, 2007 May 24; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - May 31, 2007 FY2007 Jean-Louis Cohen on Le Corbusier, 2007 May 31; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - July 2008 Accounting Report, 2008 July; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - July 2008 Accounting Report, 2008 July; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - May 2008 Accounting Report, 2008 May; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - June 2008 Accounting Report, 2008 June; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - September - October 2008 Accounting Report, 2008 September - 2008 October; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - April 2008 Accounting Report, 2008 April; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - May 2008 Accounting Report, 2008 May; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - October 2008 Accounting Report, 2008 October; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - October 2008 Accounting Report, 2008 October; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - November 2008 Accounting Report, 2008 November; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - September 2008 Accounting Report, 2008 September; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - August 2008 Accounting Report, 2008 August; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - August 2008 Accounting Report, 2008 August; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Public Program Refund Request, 2008; Series 1 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - June 4, 2007 FY2007 Andrew Bolton on Poiret, 2007 June 4; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - June 5, 2007 FY2007 Olga Hirshhorn Collection Tour, 2007 June 5; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - June 6, 2007 FY2007 Christopher Janney: Architecture of the Air, 2007 June 6; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - June 10, 2007 FY2007 Letitia Baldridge on Taste, 2007 June 10; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - June 11, 2007 FY2007 Peter Mackeith on Alvar Aalto at Finland, 2007 June 11; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - June 13, 2007 FY2007 Modern House Tour, 2007 June 13; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - June 14, 2007 FY2007 Jenny Lind, 2007 June 14; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - June 20, 2007 FY2007 Peter Som, 2007 June 20; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - June 21, 2007 FY2007 Meryle Secrest Shoot the Widow, 2007 June 21; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - July 9, 2007 FY2008 Gail Levin on Edward Hopper, 2007 July 9; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - July 11, 2007 FY2008 Visit to Kreeger and Glenstone, 2007 July 11; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - July 12, 2007 FY2007 Marisa Bourgoin on the Clark Collection, 2007 July 12; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - July 17, 2007 FY2008 Word / Dance / Theater, 2007 July 17; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - July 24, 2007 FY2008 Bauhaus Evening at Germany Residence, 2007 July 24; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - July 25, 2007 FY2008 Best Cellars European Wine Class, 2007 July 25; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - July 27, 2007 FY2008 Trip to Kentuck Knob Fallingwater, 2007 July 27; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - September 13, 2007 FY2008 Helvetica, 2007 September 13; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - September 17, 2007 FY2008 Milton Esterow, 2007 September 17; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - September 20, 2007 FY2008 Ric Burns on Ansel Adams, 2007 September 20; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - September 23, 2007 FY2008 Contemporary Music Forum, 2007 September 23; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - September 25, 2007 FY2008 Sally Martin Cabaret, 2007 September 25; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - September 27, 2007 FY2008 Tim Gunn, 2007 September 27; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - October 1, 2007 FY2008 Art:21 Art In The Twenty-First Century, 2007 October 1; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - October 4, 2007 FY2008 Understanding Eliot Noyes CANCELED, 2007 October 4; Series 1 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - April 3, 2006 FY2006 Richard Greenberg Celebration, 2006 April 3; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - April 4, 2006 FY2006 Dinner at the Residence of the Ambassador of Mexico, 2006 April 4; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - April 10, 2006 FY2006 Paul Greenhalgh, 2006 April 10; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - April 18, 2006 FY2006 The Renoir Returns Cosmos Club and the Phillips Collection, 2006 April 18; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - April 23, 2006 FY2006 Contemporary Music Forum, 2006 April 23; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - April 24, 2006 FY2006 Antoine Predock, 2006 April 24; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - April 26, 2006 FY2006 Private Collections in Baltimore, 2006 April 26; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - April 28, 2006 FY2005 Weilerstein Trio, 2006 April 28; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - April 29 And May 6, 2006 FY2006 Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, 2006 April 29 and May 6; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - CANCELED May 1, 2006 FY2006 May Day in Annapolis / Bus Trip, 2006 May 1; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - May 2, 2006 FY2006 Dorothea Dietrich on Dada, 2006 May 2; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - May 5, 2006 FY2006 Festa Della Voce - Liederabend Concert, 2006 May 5; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - May 8, 2006 FY2006 Dudley Lecture - Burt Glinn, 2006 May 8; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - May 10, 2006 FY2006 Concert at the Residence of the Ambassador of Iceland, 2006 May 10; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - May 12, 2006 FY2005 Daedalus Quartet, 2006 May 12; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - CANCELED May 15, 2006 FY2006 Donald Kuspit, 2006 May 15; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - May 22, 2006 FY2006 Alan Hess Oscar Niemeyer Houses, 2006 May 22; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - May 23, 2006 FY2006 Fall Fashion Preview with FGI, 2006 May 23; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - May 31, 2006 FY2006 Chris Witcombe on the Da Vinci Code, 2006 May 31; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - CANCELED June 5, 2006 FY2006 Joshua Prince Ramus and Erez Ella, 2006 June 5; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - CANCELED June 6, 2006 FY2006 Putting on a World Premiere Musical with Round House Theatre, 2006 June 6; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - CANCELED June 8, 2006 FY2006 House of Swedan Tour, 2006 June 8; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - June 7, 2006 FY2006 Gordon Parks' Life and Work, 2006 June 7; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - June 14, 2006 FY2006 Black Tie Dinner at the Residence of the Ambassador of Egypt, 2006 June 14; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - June 14, 2006 FY2006 Black Tie Dinner at the Residence of the Ambassador of Egypt, 2006 June 14; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - June 15, 2006 FY2006 Jenny Lind, 2006 June 15; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - June 20, 2006 FY2006 McInturff Modern Apartments Tour, 2006 June 20; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - June 22, 2006 FY2006 Sheila Brady L1087, 2006 June 22; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - CANCELED 5/26 FY2006 Museum Trip to NYC, 2006 June 9; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - June 29, 2006 FY2006 Edith Piaf, 2006 June 29; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - November 9, 2006 FY2007 André Leon Talley, 2006 November 9; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - CANCELED 9/6 FY2007 Diner at the Embassy of Indonesia, 2006 September; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - November 3, 2006 FY2007 MES: Quatuor Ebene, 2006 November 3; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - November 8, 2006 FY2007 Block Club: Dreiser - Sister Carrie, 2006 November 8; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - November 12, 2006 FY2007 Contemporary Music Forum, 2006 November 12; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - November 13, 2006 FY2007 Steve Ross, 2006 November 13; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - November 15, 2006 FY2007 Hirshenson and Jenkins - A Star is Found, 2006 November 15; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - November 16, 2006 FY2007 Christo and Jeanne-Claude, 2006 November 16; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - November 28, 2006 FY2007 John Berendt, 2006 November 28; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - November 30, 2006 FY2007 Spring Trends with Mary Lou Luther/ FGI, 2006 November 30; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - December 4, 2006 FY2007 Bill Dunlap, Julia Reed Rick Gruber, 2006 December 4; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - December 5, 2006 FY2007 Marlene Ver Planck Cabaret, 2006 December 5; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Ddecember 6, 2006 FY2007 Nicholas Angelich, 2006 December 6; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - December 7, 2006 FY2007 Kevin Harty: The Reel Maid of Orleans, 2006 December 7; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - December 11, 2006 FY2007 Embassy of Swedan Visit, 2006 December 11; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Decembber 12, 2006 FY2007 Lisa Roberts: Antiques of the Future, 2006 December 12; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - December 13, 2006 FY2007 Ned Rifkin on Contemporary Art, 2006 December 13; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - December 14, 2006 FY2007 Fashion Trip To New York, 2006 December 14; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Rescheduled Jan. 29, 2007 FY2007 Andrea Mitchell: Talking Back..., 2007 January 29; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - January 17, 2007 FY2007 Fashion Copyrighting With FGI, 2007 January 17; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - January 18, 2007 FY2007 Evening At Embassy of Romania, 2007 January 18; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - January 19, 2007 FY2007 Mes: Laufman-Kurkowicz-Laufman Trio, 2007 January 19; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - January 22, 2007 FY2007 The World of Charles Dickens, 2007 January 22; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - January 22, 2007 FY2007 Ruder Brahimi Jazz, 2007 January 22; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - January 23, 2007 FY2007 Appreciating Chamber Music, 2007 January 23; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - January 25, 2007 FY2007 Kay Unger, 2007 January 25; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - CANCELED February 20, 2007 FY2007 Alexandre Tharaud, 2007 February 20; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - CANCELED February 20, 2007 FY2007 Dancing with tthe Corcoran, 2007 February 20; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - CANCELED February 5, 2007 FY2007 E.R. Braithwaite John Andrews, 2007 February 5; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - February 1, 2007 FY2007 Conversation with Robert Hughes, 2007 February 1; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - February 6, 2007 FY2007 Chamber Music Appreciation Class, 2007 February 6; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - February 7, 2007 FY2007 Joel Achenbach, 2007 February 7; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - February 9, 2007 FY2007 Mes: Alexander Quartet, 2007 February 9; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - February 11, 2007 FY2007 Contemporary Music Forum, 2007 February 11; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - February 12, 2007 FY2007 Modernism Book Club: The The Lighthouse, 2007 February 12; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - February 21, 2007 FY2007 The Changing Face of Shakespeare, 2007 February 21; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - February 27, 2007 FY2007 George Stevens, Jr., 2007 February 27; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 37)
  - Night Day September 2002, 2002 September; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Night Day October 2002, 2002 October; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Night Day November 2002, 2002 November; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Night Day December 2002, 2002 December; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Night Day July 2002, 2002 July; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Night Day January 2003, 2003 January; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Night Day February 2003, 2003 February; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Night Day March 2003, 2003 March; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Night Day April 2003, 2003 March; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Night Day May 2003, 2003 May; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Night Day June 2003, 2003 June; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Night Day July 2003, 2003 July; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Night Day September 2003, 2003 September; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Night Day October 2003, 2003 October; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Night Day November 2003, 2003 November; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Night Day December 2003, 2003 December; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Night Day January 2004, 2004 January; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Night Day February 2004, 2004 February; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Night Day March 2004, 2004 March; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Night Day April 2004, 2004 April; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Night Day May 2004, 2004 May; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Night Day June 2004, 2004 June; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Night Day July 2004, 2004 July; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Night Day September 2004, 2004 September; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Night Day October 2004, 2004 October; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Night Day November 2004, 2004 November; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Night Day December 2004, 2004 December; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Night Day January 2005, 2005 January; Series 1 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Corcoran Public Programs February 2005, 2005 February; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Corcoran Public Programs March 2005, 2005 March; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Corcoran Public Programs April 2005, 2005 April; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Corcoran Public Programs May 2005, 2005 May; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Corcoran Public Programs June 2005, 2005 June; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Corcoran Public Programs July 2005, 2005 July; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Corcoran Public Programs September 2005, 2005 September; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Corcoran Public Programs October 2005, 2005 October; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Corcoran Public Programs November 2005, 2005 November; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Corcoran Public Programs December 2005, 2005 December; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Corcoran Public Programs January 2006, 2006 January; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Corcoran Public Programs February 2006, 2006 February; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Corcoran Public Programs March 2006, 2006 March; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Corcoran Public Programs April 2006, 2006 April; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Corcoran Public Programs April 2006, 2006 May; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Corcoran Public Programs July 2006, 2006 July; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Corcoran Public Programs September 2006, 2006 September; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Corcoran Public Programs October 2006, 2006 October; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Corcoran Public Programs November 2006, 2006 November; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Corcoran Public Programs December 2006, 2006 December; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Corcoran Public Programs January 2007, 2007 January; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Corcoran Public Programs February 2007, 2007 February; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Corcoran Public Programs March 2007, 2007 March; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Corcoran Public Programs April 2007, 2007 April; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Corcoran Public Programs May 2007, 2007 May; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Corcoran Public Programs June 2007, 2007 June; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Corcoran Public Programs July 2007, 2007 July; Series 1 (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - The Family Jams, 2010 October 26; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Stealing the Ghent Altarpiece, 2010 October 13; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - DC's Own: Art of Washington Color School Movement, 2010 November; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Danish String Quartet, 2010 October; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Haunted Houses, 2010 November; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Pasion Gitana, 2010 November; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Ippolita, 2010 November; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Rick Valicenti's Thirst, 2010 October; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Chuck Close: Printmaking Techniques for Education, 2010 July 8; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Bruce Davidson: Outside Inside, 2010 October; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Pulp to Paper Workshops, 2010 July 10; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Frances Elkins Avant-Gard Interiors, 2010 July 13; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - National Museum of the American Indian, Circa 2005-2010; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Persistance of Vision: The Illusion of Motion, 2010 July 14; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - The Art of the Steal, 2010 June 8; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - JWM Turner, 2010 April 22; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Muybridge The Evolution of Landscape, 2010 April 7; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Modern Masters Bus Tour, 2010 March; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - En Plien Air Sketching, 2010 April 24; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Klavier Trio, 2010 April; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Interpreting Helios, 2010 April 20; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - East/West Blues, 2010 April 19; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - En Plien Air Sketching, 2010 April 24; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Verge Ensemble, 2010 April 25; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - Mihkel Poll, 2010 May 10; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Night Gallery: Behind the Projections, 2010 November; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - Community Art Projects Free Summer Saturdays 2010, 2010 June - 2010 August; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - An Evening with Philip Glass, 2010 September 9; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 28)
  - Verge Ensemble, 2010 September 19; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 29)
  - Educator Workshop: Architecture as Art, 2010 September 11; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 30)
  - Puttin on the Ritz: Steve Ross, 2010 September 20; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 31)
  - Seymar Chwast, 2010 September 22; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 32)
  - Tim Hetherington: Infidel, 2010 October; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 33)
  - American Modern: Inspirations for Classic Style, 2010 May 17; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 34)
  - I Love NYC Design Bus Tour, 2010 July 30; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 35)
  - Art Architecture: Photo Safari, 2010 July 31; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 36)
  - Chuck Close Film, 2010 July 21; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 37)
  - Ariel Quartet, 2010 May 2; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 38)
  - Light, Color, and Paint, Oh My! Family Workshop, 2011 February; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 39)
  - Color Painting's Pedigree, 2011 February 24; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 40)
  - Oh! The Places We Go!, 2011 February 24; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 41)
  - Roger Gastman Takes to the STreets, 2011 February 13; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 42)
  - Give Me Yourr Hand, 2011 February 13; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 43)
  - Oh, The Places We Go!, 2011 February 11; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 44)
  - Corcoran American Art and Arts 101, 2010 February 12; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 45)
  - MES: Klavier Trio Amsterdam, 2011 February 4; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 46)
  - The Cool School, 2011 February 3; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 47)
  - MES: Ariel Quartet with Roger Tapping, 2011 January 28; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 48)
  - Clouds at the Corcoran, 2011 January 22; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 49)
  - Corcoran American Art or Arts 101, 2011 January 13; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 50)
  - The Nature of Art: The Worrk of John Alexander, 2010 December; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 51)
  - Campion Platt: Made to Order, 2011 May 2; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 52)
  - Encouraging American Genius, 2011 March 31; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 53)
  - Verge Ensemble, 2011 April 17; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 54)
  - Express Yourself!, 2011 April 16; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 55)
  - Art Now! Teaching with 21st Century Art, 2011 April 2; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 56)
  - MES: Hugo Wolf Quartet, 2011 March 25; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 57)
  - Culture Wars, 2011 March 26; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 58)
  - The Picture Stories of Ben Katchor, 2011 March 26; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 59)
  - Vincent Scully: AN Art Historian Among Architects, 2011 March 21; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 60)
  - Changing the Shape of Things, 2011 March 19; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 61)
  - Corcoran American Art Arts 101, 2011 March 10; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 62)
  - Joan Mitchell: Portrait of An Abstract Painter, 2011 January 27; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 63)
  - Preserving the Washington Color School Paintings, 2011 March 3; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 64)
  - The Artful Garden, 2011 March 1; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 65)
  - Loose Documents, Circa 2005-2011; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 66)
  - San Miguel Deposits, Circa 2005-2011; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 67)
  - Bill Cunningham New York, 2011 November; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 68)
  - Say it Big!, 2011 July 23; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 69)
  - Azar Nafisi, 2011 July 13; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 70)
  - Collins, Terrence W. (empty), Circa 2005-2011; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 71)
  - Close, Chuck (Empty), Circa 2005-2011; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 72)
  - Christenberry, William (empty), Circa 2005-2011; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 73)
  - Gaia, 2011 June 24; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 74)
  - Summer Teacher INstitute, 2011; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 75)
  - Verna Curtis, 2011 June 23; Series 1 (Box 66, Folder 76)